{
    "subject": "resource/American_Vacuum_Society",
    "predicate": "ontology/language",
    "object": "resource/English_language",
    "human_readable": "The language of the American Vacuum Society is English.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9849933385848999,
            "question": "Is English the official language of the American Vacuum Society?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8781189322471619,
            "question": "What language does the American Vacuum Society use?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8755106329917908,
            "question": "Does the American Vacuum Society use any other languages besides English?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8037824630737305,
            "question": "Is English a significant factor in joining and participating in the American Vacuum Society?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7703695297241211,
            "question": "Is there a specific language required for membership in the American Vacuum Society?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7348776459693909,
            "question": "What language is primarily used for communication within the American Vacuum Society?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6780369281768799,
            "question": "If you wanted to understand the materials published by the American Vacuum Society, what language would you need to know?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6688022613525391,
            "question": "In what language are meetings and publications of the American Vacuum Society conducted?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46528762578964233,
            "question": "What is the primary mode of communication within the American Vacuum Society?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3568890392780304,
            "question": "Would someone speaking Spanish be able to easily understand materials from the American Vacuum Society?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The language of the American Vacuum Society is English.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2861_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the primary mode of communication within the American Vacuum Society?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2861_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what language are meetings and publications of the American Vacuum Society conducted?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2861_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If you wanted to understand the materials published by the American Vacuum Society, what language would you need to know?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2861_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2861_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2861_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2861_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2861_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2861_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2861_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2861_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2861_130.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2861_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2861_65.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the structured JSON format with the evaluation:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that the \"Language(s) of collection\" for both the records and miscellaneous publications collections from the American Vacuum Society are listed as English. Therefore, the statement that the language of the American Vacuum Society is English is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}